So, in this video we're going to take a quick look at how to
在这个视频中 我们来简单看一下
use the workspaces in the classroom.
如何使用教室的 Workspace
And so, this is an example of one of
这里就是一个你即将练习的 Jupyter Notebook
A couple of quick things about the workspace is that
Workspace 需要了解几个操作要点
I usually open up this tab so I can see exactly where I'm at in the classroom.
我通常都会打开这里的导航栏 这样就可以明确了解到目前的位置
If your workspace fails to load,
如果你的 Workspace 加载失败
it might be useful to click around and then come back to it or just refresh the page.
可以点击去别的页面再回来 或者直接刷新页面
And the other thing that you can do is reset or refresh the workspace itself,
还可以使用下方的菜单栏重置或刷新 Workspace
So, these are most commonly used if your workspace fails to load.
这些方法可以用来解决无法加载的情况
But once your workspace is loaded,
Workspace 加载好之后
you should be able to use it just as if it was a notebook on your local machine.
你就可以像在本地计算机上一样使用 Notebook
You'll notice that you have all of the tabs of a regular Jupyter Notebook.
可以看到这里的菜单项与常规的 Jupyter Notebook 一样
And also if you hit this Jupyter icon,
如果点击页面左上方的 Jupyter 图标
it'll take you behind the scenes of,
将会转到幕后
like, everything that you have available.
可以看到文件夹里所有的内容
And, the case of this workspace,
在这个示例 Workspace 中
you can see that there is a solution.
可以看到有一个解决方案
And here is what looks like an empty notebook,
这个看上去好像是一个空的 Notebook
and then another solution notebook,
然后是另一个解决方案 Notebook
and it's empty notebook, that's what we had before.
又是一个空的 Notebook 也就是我们刚才打开的页面
And then, some other files back here,
最后还有一些文件
like some data files and some testing files for the code
数据文件和一些用于测试学员代码的测试文件
And, if we were to click through this,
我们现在试试点击文件
so I'll just click through the, to the solution one.
比如 点击这个解决方案文件
So, a lot of times in the workspace,
大部分 Workspace 中
you'll see those in the back here,
都可以在目录中看到有对应的解决方案
so if you get stuck you can check out the solution,
如果你遇到困难 可以来查看解决方案
but also within the individual notebook.
不过 在每个 Notebook 文件中也会有一些提示
So, if we run these, so here you can see we're just reading in some data.
如果运行这些代码 你会看到我们读取了一些数据
And, if we go to the first part it says,
到问题 1 的部分
this should get the description.
你会先看到一些描述
Here's the input, so it looks like we're creating this function.
这里是 输入 看起来我们要构建这个函数
And there's like a way for you to test.
看起来还可以测试
So, I'm just going to cheat.
我现在偷个懒
But if we wanted to,
不过如果需要
we could look at the solution here and by
你都可以在这里查看解决方案
running the first two cells you can see that basically it gives a description,
运行了前两个单元格之后 可以在这里看到一些描述
so here's a way that you can test your code.
在这里你可以测试你的代码
As you go through this particular program,
在随后的课程中
there are lots of tests that tell you, nice job,
你会看到很多测试结果 Nice job 是说正确完成了
that you got it right or oftentimes like error.
不过经常也会遇到报错
So, this first part is just to see if you're getting the thing that you expect.
所以 这里只是检查代码是否符合预期
And then, we have a lot of.
然后 在这里我们还有很多的测试
So, if you'll notice up here,
上面可以看到
we read in test1 is t. So,
我们导入了 test1 并用 t 来表示
there are a whole bunch of tests in that file that will check
test1 包含了很多测试代码
your code against our solutions and make sure that they match up,
用来检查你的答案是否与解决方案中的答案一致
and if they don't, we'll try to give you feedback as
如果不一致 我们会尝试提供
to what we think you should do differently to get them to match.
一些针对性的提示
Yeah, so that's the main thing,
主要就是这些
is that if you go back here,
如果回到这里
there's a whole bunch of files.
你会看到很多文件
In general, we'll have it so it pops up to the file
通常默认显示的是对应当前课程内容的练习文件
But it's also the case that you can upload your own files so you'll
不过你也可以上传自己的文件
notice that there's an upload button here where you can
通过这里的 Upload (上传) 按钮
connect your own workbooks and bring them into the classroom.
将自己的文件上传到教室中
Or you can create new Python or text files within
或者也可以在这里创建新的 Python 或者 文本文档
here as well and save them into this particular workspace.
然后保存在特定的 Workspace 中
Notice you can hit this Jupyter icon from your notebook,
注意 你可以点击 Jupyter 图标
and select any of the files,
然后选中任何一个文件
and then choose to download them.
选择 Download 该文件
So, you can download individual files to your machine and then run them locally.
这样就可以下载单独的文件 在本地计算机上运行
If you would prefer to do that as opposed to working in the classroom.
如果你更愿意在本地计算机完成练习的话
I've also provided a link down below
如果你不想一个一个下载
this video in case you don't want to download these one at a time.
我在视频下方还提供了一个下载链接
Again, just a quick recap,
最后 简单地回顾一下
you can see that there's individual notebooks
你可以在这里看到每一个单独的 Notebook 练习
and solutions as well as the data back here.
其对应的解决方案 以及数据文件
When you are in any individual notebook,
在每一个单独的 Notebook 里
you should be able to run that just like you would from your local machine.
你应该可以像在本地计算机上一样运行文件
And so, with this particular example you should
所以在这个特定的示例中
be able to run the cells just like you would on
你可以像在本地一样运行单元格
your own machine and we've built tests to
而且我们有专门的测试代码
sort of make sure that you're on the right track with your notebook.
帮助你纠正代码里的错误
If you do get stuck,
如果你遇到了任何困难
you'll notice that in the back you can take a look at
可以在文件夹里查看解决方案文件
the solution files or even look at the solutions that you're running up against,
或者直接对比测试代码中的正确答案
to see why you might be missing something or
纠正自己答案中的错误
how we computed our solution in the background, great.
或者查看幕后是如何对比检查答案的
Well, I hope this was useful as a way to see how to use the notebooks in the classroom.
最后 我希望这些介绍能帮助你学会使用教室的 Notebook
In general, if you're comfortable with
总的来说 如果你熟悉 IPython Notebook 的话
this should feel very similar to that situation.
应该不会对这个环境感到陌生
And, yeah, thanks for joining me.
感谢观看